Thank you Ron thank you not get me down
and then the hamburger joint and then you
got to learn where the cracker is a not
a right. That's all funny thing up the
road just good lookin Dame sittin in
a car all alone now what would you feel
justice she was doing nothing just sitting
there I got
a rule about women they
reckon I lost my mom. And
me to disturb you miss just want to be
sure everything was OK. Excuse me lady
but are you sure you're all right.
I wish you luck here than she did I just
checked on her up the road without you got
a strange where. I better call an ambulance
I doubt if it's serious and I'm as good
as doctors you'll find it this
time of night let's take grins.
Well no bones broken bruises that's OK I
think you better rest you for the night
and surprised your beautiful young woman
in an accident you haven't asked for
a mirror. Perhaps that fits with the way
you were driving tonight that you find the
idea of living not very attractive is that
any of the things. That Matter of fact
it is my business I happen to be
a psychiatrist I don't think that.
Mind if I disagree with you.
There's
a beautiful young woman fairly well to do
or be in good physical condition but just
doesn't care what happens to it this is
interesting not altogether unusual but
interesting course there are the obvious
deductions it's not that duck and I prefer
to run it back out you don't want anyone
to see inside or if you don't even want to
take
a look yourself many women haven't the
courage to face themselves so they look for
escape in one excitement after another my
patients are like that I'm not going to
be a patient. To tell you I'm
a challenge. Because. It
will drive you to stick.
It To Me And you're an intelligent woman
not an idiot but you promise me one thing
. When you get ready to throw yourself or
Brooklyn Bridge when you come and see me
first. Back.
Up what is
a problem but I want to know are probably
as much damage to me and again these are
pretty as a picture of a stubborn
as a mule. But this time with
a lot more of them. Coming
to me and we were just ripping you up back
a little bit so I guess nothing First
it was about Mr Carter a couple O.
Yes he runs
a drone I tell you your own correspondent
company London Paris first then you may
remember him as one of our biggest
advertiser all what you really want to say I
know what you really want to say our way
to know what Charlie wants to say he wants
to know why I killed the OP layout
a mistake cost him famous
duel and I understand the
a phone number goes to press without it
that's right in the first place it's not
great sages dream but
the result is we stand
a good chance of losing the corporate
accounts time I run in my department I might
not have considered that
he was doing it but I had
a talk with Gordon he was decidedly yes
with about it I'm not interested in cotton
but if this magazine is going to submit
to advertisers like me I cannot bought it
now please Miss Damien That's the promise
to Mr Crane and you better get someone
else to take my place Peter statement just
a moment gentlemen if you don't find I talk
to you later. I thought I should bring
this to your attention gambling with the
drugs going to grow up no harm done just
a. Matter of course of
or worked up from today.
To get your drink no thanks
I don't know what is this
private blackmail of yours threatened to
quit in order to win an argument I just
assume quickly I mean not tell me what's
happened your wound up bother or nothing.
You know I don't want to quit I will go
to my personal feelings that you are the
best are headed over the
head. And I promise
a new sleeping pill red one this red pill
is to put you to sleep why pills to wake
you up from somebody since with my idea
what I'm doing this evening that English
friend found him pretty again if
I couldn't get out and to take
a leave using some of the stories
thanks not let him be the last to have
a problem madmen. They're a
bundle of lies that ended up in
a bun beautifully tied together I'm trying
to be honest that you won't believe me
when you buy their. Because I don't
really think about yourself.
Why do you have to go back a bit for
thirty Fancher and even give me
a chance to make love to you you know me
knowing I. You know something. Far behind
making love makes more money than I do.
Much easier if you made love to me what it
. Got me to brush your bright sunshine
and make them the family that.
You are pretty as your very own no bones
broken. Now see you at the office then.
Join your somebody and. What
is actually. There and.
When you have to dance for that Polly was.
No you're not doing I always feel for
security when I'm with you. And I
take so you're the love surest pain
in the neck. I'm going. You know I'm going
to look out on me come on for yourself
I've told you I'm going to leave that me
you can't leave me just sitting here in
the snow I'm mad about you
in my own foul way. But not.
Any chance of getting it can you promise
to overtake me and hear someone I know
your faces to meet Mr Felix court one of
our most prominent advertisers and you
doomsday. To get this so don't be just
content. They are all about you hope it
wasn't that. Oh you needn't worry I always
from my own future. And I give you
a lift anywhere my car just on time.
Thank you for getting me catch.
Phrase time. I'm sorry
Mr You mean there is no
time around here thinking me sort of.
You know you don't want to live. Well
that doesn't seem to be any of them.
Going to Mr Garrett. Good night of course.
I wasn't very polite and now there was
Garrick for that matter how he always enjoys
uncomfortable situations to feel
uncomfortable. You know. Frankly I don't
know to learn you know what not
to talk about and now now.
Begin to mash knows I have been
doing the business that runs so as
a matter of fact you don't
look like amounted to like
a work of art. That layout
on your toes is still
a wretched piece of copy I can only admire
your potato and I'm still not going to I
wouldn't time to spread the word
of. This because I think you're
a bit dangerous. There and it
was it was so the proof is I'm
a very ordinary. I'm
sorry I forgot to give you my address my
fault I've got to ask you or you're coming
from me and no I don't think so but you
really must see those jewels you've been
telling that much and some of them the
photographs. Need you in about fifteen
minutes but I said I wasn't coming
you know you did so you did.
Let me take you right where I
want to stay and cool off.
But I want to read this place
a long time in fact I'm pretty good to
read that you found out from the. Oh it's
not so hard to take once you get the hang
of it. I think I know all the troubles
that come with money. And all that.
Well if you've got me all figured out.
Only what I'm seeing here good folks
pick two but I can't look at them do I'm
alone invention and I spend hours here all
by myself poring over old manuscripts
get on expect that. To be my heart.
Was ripped from Damian you know the.
Best thing. Is that I remember when he
came in to paint that picture of my mother
everybody was fascinated by him especially
mother Bobby and by chasing him out of
the house I'm afraid that three years of
me and. My father was very much to number
line that's hanging from an optics lucidly
here but you're going to show me your.
Own yours of course I forgot that's
the reason we came in here wasn't it.
You wanted to have
a plan and came in this way in one of my
darkest secrets. You really want to see
that do. Not take in the name I
cannot bring him from the diamond.
One present. But then very few people
are going to dinner and I'm going to.
Have another drink.
You know you need to relax I'm sober next
thing I knew your nerves nothing like
rubber band I'm never surprised to
see. Your many curious mixture I
name are like that it's not me
that's not my man mind I now had
a man one. Desperate guys.
One of the shadows.
Insomnia. Got.
Me a second. Baby and gone. Now with
a cotton she's not here yet you I have
a calling. You know. We're
never going to get. You
sent leave to feed
a cough in the court I'm very
interesting you never residentially.
Yet but given it any thought I could
have predicted it. Gratis I run my back
she got
a new boyfriend I got some got to have not
done all the time yeah right here today
gone tomorrow. Personally I don't see what
you see it all that it comes out of your
nose I didn't hire you to gossip about my
private life you know me to. Go get your
money yes through.
Here too many of. Us We are going
to be we find it hard you work
for. Me Don't you about me. Court
what you worry baby off expect.
Understand you by July that's right do
ya do you I don't like people to gossip
about me. You don't know I don't but
it's pretty late to be thinking about
a thing like that and so rotten to take it
on your secretary get on you don't think
your life is
a secret do you boys are betting eight to
five this morning because the layout to
be in the next issue of the. Medal Why
don't you get wise to yourself everybody
else is one romance after another that
your whole life and what your get out you
try to dress it up with pretty words which
you don't fool anybody they know what
you are and you will never change gaf you
don't care because it's too much fun.
It isn't true it is.
Just a good Here's
a beautiful just doesn't
care what happens to. Many
women having the courage to face the same.
So they look for escape and when they
started to know.
That you find the idea of living
not very nice. I want to hear your
stuff I can.
I'm glad I was right and
intelligent woman not need. To do
that now if you feel like
talking just go with it until
you're afraid don't you but it's our job
to find out why to explore the shadows and
throw light on what we find and you'll
be able to see yourself clearly and face
yourself honestly when you can
do that you won't be afraid and.
I was living my fans. Mother
and father can come there.
And I can and can they know where
he lived came from that one.
There was
a successful painting when I.
Went his own way to try to play
just as you've been trying to do. It
was to make him so very happy when I
was certain he was bad best man in
the won't until. Until he killed
himself and you couldn't understand
what he did. Understand now.
I think I do. Did you ever do anything to
yourself I used to play you give it up
I didn't pay enough and besides I didn't
want to be my father I wanted violence and
have you been living your own life. I
have the kind of life you really want
I don't know I don't know don't you think
you've been hiding here so did you ever
try and discover the person you really
were deep down underneath I never can't
because. I'm not so sure I don't know. In
this case I'm afraid I can't help you.
Cause that's entirely up
to you. So we go on then
I was doing what I wanted to pay my
own way and making my own. Nobody was
nobody but yourself and they didn't really
make you happy did it wasn't because
down underneath you knew there was something
missing something important. That
would worry you wouldn't and then you would
drug yourself with the excitement of
more excess. But I know the pattern
of behavior is suffering from
a disease of the time and your outlook
malady is common place is probably got the
Suppose for
a moment that you were an alcoholic
that much the same you know unsure of
themselves underneath and seeking reassurance
from you except. Instead of getting
it because the drug could solve this problem
by taking another drink this of course
is no solution and eventually we find you
scroll hopelessly at the bar without the
strength or even the desire to say I can't
accommodate you're not helping me doing
something. You've been insulting yourself
in this day me I'm insulting your body
I'm insulting your soul. Your life
hasn't been gay and glamorous
a pole it's just been muddled them senseless
you know that you know and if you
really want to change it you can start
right away. Now it's up to you.
You can never comment on the rents paid to
end up that mom Downing auntie and I can
vouch out we know we are. Not implanted
with Damien Duff it. Now now she still has
to come in the car and
when I don't now exactly
a danger in the day out. To the ng out the
head good let me call him back and you
may be sorry may have everything in this
final turn without comment this time and
ask to see more of that work and these you
may be able to but you haven't given me
on you would know I'm not giving anyone
momentum beautiful Would you mind popping
off for a minute that just sixty seconds
feel better tell. Madeleine what
a jam I'm going to raise and
want to be able to know as
a player expect me to do it and I thought
you might talk of course I'm sure but
you're here for the rest of nicely you're
really quite have great time but man and
I'm in debt up to here I
only make a hundred dollars
a week and you know I can't live on
that five thousand dollars doesn't mean
a thing to Courtney you better get out
of here the file goes my temper you're
forcing me to say things that I don't want
to say but if you're going to act cold
and virtue was
a bonnet you'll hear them Suppose I
told Kranish tell him what about
court you know you've got a very
nice job here but you won't have
a very long if I tell cremation I don't
want to tell him but. But so funny
as
a black male you have to get far gone tell
him pending what I write and you are and
he is gone use my phone if you want at my
desk at my office I'm through with them.
For about Marcus is no mistake
and has an inbox just
a moment. I'm sorry she doesn't
like you anymore he might turn her
whole world like
a pot. Full of apartments steamy and
Oh no she gave up her apartment.
I want to try the post office.
Thing in there Richard Phillips one
thirty seven West fifty three.
But nothing doing seven was
Damien has taken my advice as
a doctor you've been living in an area of
infection and she's removed yourself from
it I take it you've been sitting me part
of the general compare my nation when you
come here for information not
diagnosis I usually charge
a fee for insulting people I'm willing
to pay for data of any kind yes I gather
that but I have nothing for sale I suppose
you are being very ethical but I'd like
to talk to Madeleine and your presence
if you wish Ms Damien is living under
a different name in
a different world she told me to tell you
if you inquire that she was busy growing
a new soul would you please keep
off the grass for buns to cook by
a doctor of the devil why are you playing
the Almighty in this fashion not
particularly I'm used to it.
Wolf.
Possibly better than talking so you think
I've done that you wouldn't care if you
get the hint I only hope the new tenant
will like it seems awful particular he's
a floor walker may see what you can always
get that you'll never sell it you know
take my advice try something more cheerful
go like ours in Butterfly. Thank you Mrs
guy get.
My save my life. Yes this is going to
go or get my summer what do you see my.
Post about it is part of my own work really
shouldn't bring these problems of the
lab but well I'm going to cut
a thank you. But. When I
spoke to scream Thank you for the money
well you know the next coming up.
But I mean nothing like I.
Come in. Oh oh so you're an artist on June
when I don't know oh Mr Geiger said yesterday
that you were given authority if I
was low and I was wondering could you do
a job for me. I want your part to think
of me No no nothing like that I'm doing
some research and it has to be able straight
What do you want me to draw. Nothing
fancy just blood cells and things
sounds fascinating Oh it is really
you see it's a lot like oh no
I know you'll be surprised
a really is fascinating once you get in it
for someone to publish it and I couldn't
pay very much and in fact I couldn't pay
anything to the first among them down for
fun so I was also to live up to my place
but they all but I couldn't I Oh sure you
can I just live downstairs you
know the mousetrap Oh by the way
my name is because. My niece
thinks her good name is to.
Just write in my drawing and I'm not to
find out. Your take you assert oneself is.
All I want to know. So I said it's quite
good for you the lad with me the morning
is ready for the next year and I was at
twelve o'clock when I hadn't had my dinner
yet you have not at. All gosh I'm sorry but
I get I get so wound up and is going to
die but now I'm hungry. To do well
it's to meet that have brilliant
idea I get to coach
you to three solid patterns only since I
got out of the Army I was lucky to get
this job or
a surge now I've got to get it finished
then life oh then I go back to Oregon to
become the usual respectable
small town doctor know my.
Oh my. Prose and bellyache five
dollars of it maybe you're
lucky you'll get some right oh I get plenty
of rest but I don't think I'll like.
You know our time tonight
right we're meeting
a few friends at the busy bee cafeteria
we don't know Mr Bush oh well after I.
Cannot imagine who. I got on the first of
a little town in Germany while
I was still in the army I bet
a couple of Russian medical officers were
to take it away were pretty steamed up
about it. You know. We got
to go the first night over
a bottle of vodka. I remember the town
was still burning. So maybe it was the
bog Anyhow we got to talking about any
ridiculous Well I guess I got pretty excited
you mean you speak Russian over
a bottle of vodka anybody Russian government
coffee no thanks I met one. At any
rate I promised myself that night that
just as soon as the war we're. Going to do
a job. You haven't stopped to eat them and
that's an error just about the record
one hundred dollars even. Thank you.
Thank you if. You were sure you've got
everything you want oh yes thank.
You no I don't think I'd like to talk to
you Karl is the sentiment I am pancakes
and pick up more scientifically this to
kind of dive the kind the doctors prescribe
and the stuff they sell but you know we
can fetch em right here can't make sand
could take discoveries that way sure you
can take Benny you saw some flies nibbling
on
a piece of pancreas figured out there must
be sugar in them one minute he had the idea
for instance you know you're
a very lovely girl you're not
the inventor and all that I am
the very heart of science the
truth talk about it and then
and.
Oh. Say did you buy the
you know manuscript of
a yes for sure for the five much
because nothing you talk something I.
Think until you know you can buy
a pair of good mice for twenty cents. David
have someone on the phone you can just
sign the picture I know for sure but the
floor looking down fat he said it almost
as good as
a photograph but has great taste I think
it's wonderful I'm proud of. The product
itself to David because he would
take your own good looks.
It's important that I mean not just to you
but really well it won't cure all the
ills of man or beast but.
Yes I think it may be
important but I also think that I better
handed him before I start changing it
again. Like I'm alone or could die for
sure why not I think you've been drawing
blood cells long enough time now for
the me part of the face to face.
I hope your text is as good as your
distractions I hope so too so.
Well that's that you didn't tell me away
you actually didn't you didn't tell him
they were come on I'm sure my last.
Comment I would try and bring it about
your. Assistant the thought of.
Alice is me How do you like I think
it's. How do you find anything not
been here for six months that was there yes
doesn't matter anyway the boss OK's my
research out the other week
secular and yes back story.
All that way just to make
a living is it
a battle zone. Or what's the use in getting
mad when I'm so much in love with you I
can't see straight I haven't done any
work in here for days I just sit around
waiting until I can see you. Because
that's just what I can point to see you.
My darling I never felt like this
about anyone before. Tell me when
did you first know. When I saw you last
night ME TOO I'M A forget you standing in
the hall with
a mouse in your hand. Only I didn't know
then what was happening I thought I had
the flu. Will you marry me.
But when you. We don't know each other I
mean you don't pay me I hope what I do
course I know you know what I want to know
about me day because of Mt
University of Oregon kept
a Medical Reserve young healthy very
much in love. With your marriage.
Placed on
a. Plane got to ask you now.
How is that your. Case get.
Back to the compound.
I am and the
end of the
a.
Way. In
a. Way I.
Am and am.
Going. To have an answer
rather important question.
And. I wouldn't.
Blame him.
Good night.
You're better code to go out.
Again Tom I had provided me with your new
address in the propertied part time act.
You were never cast which I didn't think
in my head you see I expected to find you
Richard lonely gripping with their conflict
rather naive of me. But your please go
across our But before I do wouldn't you
like to tell me about him. I'm in love
now laugh if you're wrong. I don't feel
like. I've always wondered if it were
possible for people like you and me and
you think you really got to love eternal
the fact that the simpler the whole thing
the hurricane I'm very glad to be over
and I think I'm
a little sad for myself. So having told
him I have you know clearly more or less
about me for instance if I should have
to tell him you're absolutely right you
shouldn't men prefer to keep their you know
something please God. If you ever need
me you will let me know and you know
them don't fall apart to my name and.
Don't care what you say I'm going to marry
him just as soon as it can be arranged
you want to run away from your problem
by not coming only if you're looking for
security from someone else instead of
building it within yourself but I'm not I
can't talk to your kid don't believe me
falling in love doesn't cure everything
overnight but do you mean
let's be honest there's
a side of you that hasn't fully
changed there's no true. That is
true isn't.
It if you still not told David about
yourself I couldn't tell you let him fall in
love with an illusion with someone who
doesn't exist I could never tell not stop
loving Isn't that a risk you have to take
you know being a catalyst you can build
a lifetime relationship on the line if
you're really in love you'll tell it with
the others it was different but if you love
him will you please stop saying it how
many times about that when
you are not but real love is
a sharing if you're strong enough to face
this yourself you're strong enough to
face it with big. Cats. I can
do it the only happiness of it.
That's up to you is Dave.
Doubting your money and well it is
fine to me. Dr was right my favor.
Is what I owe you like. One really trouble
if you think it's so important he wants
me to go to Chicago and read it before the
convention Oh no more my idea I don't
want to go when all you have to me and I
got to catch the eight o'clock plan when
you come around
a few days but I tell you what soon as I
get back let's get married you can get
a license in three days and I take fifteen
minutes to get married you still want to
marry me don't you not anything you know.
You know I'm going to feel kind of
silly at this convention because it's
a great honor and all that but you realize
that I'll be talking before some of the
biggest men in the field
that's one of the I like now.
I was just thinking how I'm feeling you
didn't love me don't be silly now to Jan
say could you ever stop and that's really
a gruesome sort of course not
even you even if there was
a reason the world is bothering you now I
just want to be human sure about what.
You love me and not to be losing your Will
Talk About Me Scientists can believe in
illusions I believe in you are the best
thing that's ever happened to me for sure
so if it will be enough and I think it'll
have to be it's all I've got so much.
That just about does it. Battling
for there's something special on your
mind something that you want to tell me
just put down love.
Me. By the way write me every day any day
hope you miss me hope you suffer like
a maniac I will have problems OK you you
know I'm going to be jealous and that's
a whole lotta nobody everybody just jumps
down on down to you Don't you know that
I'm on in life because nothing will be
married the minute I get. One of the
locals here if it isn't man of
the. Hour you know it's been
a long time David just as Mr Garrett used
to work with the man Americans we want
a guy like with the record though perhaps
a record with me again doing some competent
work for me you know how you make your
. Business Mr Carson I'm David
to cut you off if you're
a very lucky man Dr I think so.
Well that my mistakes and my
congratulations to you both
thank you tonight you know.
I don't believe I'm going
to never do you get you're
a very cynical man you don't believe in
true love you don't think many windows
either do you I don't know but I've
always been fascinated by miracles.
Come in. Telegram periodically.
I thought I'd bring it
up myself I thought it might be important
that I knew. He won't be back till
Friday that meant for you you never can
count on them and I forgot Dr Somebody
called you said you were coming in from the
right she's been trying to get in touch
with you Brenda your yes. I said you got
your own reason which was to get out and
see you're free to sit in this room all
day and all night Thanks this is going to
get out of my business mind you.
This is mad that mad at
me but this is really
a voice from the dead I picked that doctor
if you want for our eyes I just have to
talk to you. Right about where you remember
that Art Caplan the one you saw when I
do need your help the arm an awful man so
I am never come into that office again as
long as I live but I wouldn't ask you to
do that just meet me somewhere would only
take an hour I promise. If
it's just the two of us.
All right I'll be there oh covered leaves
we were really desperate wonderful I'm
just dying to see you five pm She owes you
a good wonderful day and professional pride
of never. Are just out for the fish too
bad yeah I don't want you to be they wouldn't
think of spoiling your union by their
. I don't track madness Dr on no
doc no you I don't like to eat.
Oh it's very very serious very few.
I know that we didn't is this time she just
came in this big we missed your missing
Have you been awake that night
that same way. You get.
The pale that we just say you know I can't.
Stand it we'll get right to what you
shouldn't do when I don't
know you better way to leave
a mess I'm in the government are. Down
I'm just dying to hear what you want to
do with tell me. That there's nothing
to. Come on let's go to work.
You know just trying to hear you think
about the simple and practical.
Governing you used to be able to drink
a. Straining no one but now it might
be just like the old name again to
surroundings that we
can go to shout. Back.
This is
a. Good fortune writing to write
this you might. Get mad at me
making a date with you it's true that
in my record I want for the good of
a dash for it thank you Mr Jasper camera
and the artist are going to pray.
About it to be free of
whatever it is I've got
a particular meaning down the steps and
then good about the data management no day
. You'll excuse me are
you. Coming on in to.
Keep me I'm. No longer. Got
to be utterly commencing with
nothing of
a strike discrepancy his account is to
go to believe that the world owes him
a gay life no matter who pays zero zero
stranger. I don't want to. Know what he
hears he was particularly Glenda
saying we should we. Well. The
noise. Than normal run rate. They were
going on constantly running into men who
know you. Painted them are. I know what
you're thinking. The way a big
man did they not out down
a shall we say down. The. Road. For.
Me I spoke with Gordon please just
a moment or. Just
a minute.
I'm going. To get on the phone. All right.
Hello again. I have some interesting
news you know dear madam.
Consider it are you because by the way I'm
just going to have the stones in my safe
and one's missing. Out on. My
mind while. You getting it only that I
don't like thieves but you're being
ridiculous let me come over and talk about
nothing to talk about I'm taking it up
with the police but I
don't you can't do that.
Mr Garrett again so. That about going
to. I'm sorry Mr Corliss just lier.
I. Am not going to sit here again
owing to my out of explaining
because you. Know it wouldn't
approve of my going to come
down. Let's face it to change what
you have never changed out it just got
a felony was out of my. Family
. I'm finished now I'm waiting for
the privilege of their own
OK to get French T.V.
. I'm going to. Come out and you.
Hope you didn't get through what.
You know concerning. Quite
a coincidence funny you in the rain. Is.
Bad to you especially when there's no
point to it I was
a farm thing hoping. He would be. Enough
to piss the bullet though I happened to
be a beauty. Which shouldn't be
a crime in your eyes please
know the pain. I'm in
a good to know word so I'm very clear that.
You always come to me you know I beat
you and everything your stand for the fans
I may be able to improve your opinion
and your man. You know
your very thing done.
I'm not.
Going to remember you if you want but
I'm curious do you think you forgot to
mention
a significant omission that your friend
from right would say come on I'm getting so
. Down. I'm going home right
after dinner I think how wonderful
you feel when you find.
That
a big chill out in your bones maybe even
your. Typical I don't know why I'm on here
. Right. Now I'm not afraid
of Obama. You know. I work.
In this rain you must even think if
you. And you've been very annoying. Mad
and we but I figure that you know no I don't
know for sure do we feel the same way
about I don't know making sense you could
want to make this make more sense than
talking in your own family and what would
you like to add to your wonderful there
are things we could ever do
to you. But you know it.
But I tell you I'm going to raise the
money I'll tell you honest I don't like
getting with you that's a job for the
police to swear out a watch and never get
a dime but I did just that and I just
did have some money temporarily Here's
a pen I'm not interested in I want to get
a good night book out and
you've got to give me
a good night. You
gotta look at the Explain you was too
big for. Never going back I'll get
a promise I want is
a little more time couple of weeks what
are you doing when the police came from
what you want.
You. Know
a very lovely this morning when you are
thinking you know I can assure you of all
this and of the story. Please.
I. Thought I could wait till Friday I
just said money to stand out on the farm
maybe too so. I've been lost. And
I think that you can depend on
say the big news I'm a success. When I was
a man with you to look pretty good then
I think you better get back in bed. Now
that first I don't have to go back to
bellyaches in Oregon you're not marrying
a small country doctor
young lady you're marrying
a promising young research centers these
That's what Dr Broder says and he ought to
know he's got
a long white beard darling and said Come
on you could take your temperature.
Gee I wish you could have been there when
I finish reading my paper they all got
together and offered me my own laboratory
in California I still can't believe. That
is writing
a paper you'll find it on the
bottom of page ten. Where
you really are were you know what
are you some. Kind of what's my.
Darling you call as I got
a chill. Stay right here on the
back and I don't know how to be
a second I want to get
a hot water bottle and look like. This
mendicant home I don't know friends of
hers where everything was weather over
nothing right when he was in his diction
about we've found it perhaps you'd better
tell me first restriction as well and
we'll see the doctor who lives here it is
important to get you come back to morrow
it's important. Could you get some extra
blankets and what about
a friend of addiction to stand for what
is it an accident or something I wouldn't
call an accident but we should cut out this
mystery and tell me what it's all about
OK Dr. Matalan. These
men are from the police they want to take
over from here dark I'm sorry to tell you
this is Sergeant by your friend
a physics course in which your metrosexual
with the most not known I was there you
see Mr Corbett any time you know I didn't
not look which day me and we wouldn't be
here asking questions unless we already
knew most of the answers Oh wait
a minute her name's not they mean I think
you've got the wrong party I think maybe
you've got the wrong party dark the name
happens to be Damian this happens to be
a case of murder Take
a look at that newspaper. I want to know
what's going on I think this is my house
not got no sorry madam will talk to you
as long as I've been here there's never
been playing around here what you're going
to be. Not much they need to tell us
what happened last night or can you give
me pardons for the in here this guy going
to pretty sweet at each other isn't that
right how did they say it isn't true now
according to the chauffeur you got the
courthouse at one of the seven What time did
you leave but I didn't go into the house
and I met him by accident to be done look
at me I want to be on the Damien dark not
very long if you might know that he was
mixed up with this guy court and I think
it is OK so he didn't go to the house with
course I didn't he wanted me to come to
the house but I wouldn't do it when I've
been going to the house I didn't I didn't
you know you tell me at the dock here.
You get me think she came in about nine
and I can know all she was walking in the
rain
a lady said she looked kind of wild but I
caught him he was here already visitors
are a couple of weeks ago get
a you know it will tempt around midnight
anything else the landlady thought the
carbon had
a key to this place she was kind of vague
as to how you got it I didn't give you
the keys then if you can believe that I've
got to keep hearing here this one fits
yet
a chiar but I didn't get to tell you. Why
you go away but Dana don't leave me I
didn't carry my so I had didn't care who
cares whether you killed him or not.
Could asking for testing Well it is
a regulation. OK sixty six. Basically
. Lied to me you've always lied to me but
I'm not lying I didn't want to cause pain
he said to drive me home and he made love
to you didn't you don't deny it of course
you made love to you if you keep your
room. To come to me. I can do that.
If this thing were so innocent you would
have told me when I said I was in love
with you when I asked you to marry me.
I was afraid I was afraid of him but I
wouldn't. Need to Know I was
horribly changed on you maybe.
I keep on lying you tried it upstairs and
it didn't work but I was in love with you
all right I made
a mistake I thought you were something
wonderful and you turned out to be something
else so let's just forget about the only
thing that you can do for me is let me
alone. And.
Sold it in general to the jury a
prosecution would prove beyond a shadow of
a doubt that matter the baby and is guilty
of the committed the murder because
we will prove he was in his apartment but
not with murder we will prove that the
fingerprints are on the table right with
which it was murder. And we've approved
further that you had a motive for
all of it for after all this is
a very simple story to one
man Dr Carson she was
a pure and over woman to the other police
car from an irresponsible life of love
to self indulgent to be faithful to the
man she wanted to marry to weaken lacking
in character to break because
the trust of soul was spent on
a hot this just to make one man
believe what all others knew to be
a lot of men Koppen threatened
to expose us she went to his
apartment to plead with him the
only way she knew him braced
she made love to him but in spite of that
he threatened to expose the lie that she
was living to silence him forever
ladies and gentlemen of the jury
the state I asked you to find Madeline
Damien guilty guilty of murder in the first
degree on the night goes to court and
called on the defendant to let him into her
apartment I think he did not
want to get in and not to have
a key to go to keep his own why was the
defendant when he arrived out of the Dr I
suppose pulling the wool over the guy.
Thank you Mr Geiger you know what this
Mr Mitchell got to be cross-examined
no question the statement I can defend you
properly if you will get you've got to
put up
a fight. And I was the guy just
what was the nature of the work you
did to Mr Kaufman most of the crystal
confidential secretary I suppose you'd call
it and in that capacity
you were the position of
a great deal about his private life yes
of course did Mr Carter know the most
famous line to duck the cousins and concealing
the true character from him I would
rather not answer that question
Mr Brime you see both the same in
a close friend. Yes I understand.
But let's get back to the maybe the OP or
what was the attitude of the defendant on
cross and sought out because she was
embarrassed naturally. She is embarrassed now
thank goodness Mr Mitchell I've got to
cross-examine I don't we have to chop down
that no questions are you
a close friend of the defendant here than
last that you could fight and you on
matters of
a personal nature yes she did if you are
asked in this court do you think you could
recall any of those intimacy I have because
some of them in now have noted they are
not I object creation sustained but let
me ask you this Mr Royce would you say in
general that men found this Damien
attractive definite day and would you say
dismissed Damien five minutes
back to her I'm afraid I'm
a Anyone who would cover the relations
between Mr Damien and her former employer Mr
Crane each. Day in your opinion was there
anything more than friendly I'll take the
question calls for the conclusion of the
witness and his prejudicial Objection
sustained because I'm going
to day means
a patient of mine I don't have to think
she's guilty of murder do you know I don't
she may be guilty of other things but in
there she's being tried for murder and she
won't even defend herself you've got
a pretty good lawyer how she needs your
help Dr in her own mind she's not on trial
for murder she's on trial for those other
things and it's not the judge who's
trying that case it's you I don't want
to be rude Dr but I don't think you know
what you're talking about I'm sorry to
disagree you see I've been treating MS
Damien for some time I happen to be her
psychiatrist Dr Kay but I'm sorry to Bob if
you got.
Any worse because this.
Has been paid you as
a patient. If you come to her
own free will yes of course. To
a doctor the people do not go to
a psychiatrist must they consider themselves.
Well shall we say not well balanced
in general that's correct as
a matter of fact wasn't this baby and on
the verge of good but it's so aside what
you made your first visit to you your honor
I did well no matter will prove that by
other witnesses however is it not true
that people who come to his patients come
a problem objection objection
only room. When I can that be no
point in it coming to me if they didn't
have problems over the tender came to you
with
a problem do you mind telling us doctor in
your opinion just what was missed Fabian's
problem that is
a confidential matter between doctor and
patient I'm afraid I can't discuss but
during the course of your treatment of
this Damien did you ever discuss her
relationship with Dr David COUSINS Yes
we did but bearing in mind the fact that
she's engaged and that I did
not because I do think she was
a frank with you sort of as
a matter of fact I urged her to tell
him everything and if you're not to my
knowledge why not why didn't I'm afraid
you have to ask Miss Damien about that
if you ever meet Dr Carson Yes just a few
minutes ago well I'm sure you found him
a reasonable definition John man and yet
the defendant if you can find him and he
lived up to cousins I think I can see why
his Damien. Hesitated to confide in you
mind telling us why it's my impression
that Dr Cousins has the capacity either
emotionally or
intellectually to understand
a problem like Mr Damian as
the trial going down not very well I'm
afraid if the doctor questions and you are
for the stand you weren't expecting in.
A matter of fact I was expecting. A
load of it but I don't relax
Ellie is this a professional or
a social call Dr Caleb you said some pretty
rough things about me this afternoon as
I did didn't. I think I'm entitled
to an explanation for the out. As
a matter of fact I'm very glad you came
over. I want to talk to you about this
Damien I'm not interested in this to me.
I'm glad to see you're still in love with
me and I'm not in love with him all the
better than we can approach the subject and
Mr Damon is one scientist to another you
see I'm interested in this Damien because
he's a patient of mine I believe I
was well on the way to solving for
a problem it would be most distressing
to me if you were to die now for
a crime she didn't commit it would be as
though you had lost one of your white mice
one that you had just inoculated What's
all this got to do with me only this
that when you testified tomorrow you'll be
asked to tell the truth the whole truth
the whole truth about a human soul is
a complicated proposition and I'm not going
to tell you anything about this Damien
that you haven't already heard but
isn't it possible that you picked up
a few stray facts and added them up to
a conclusion that's entirely wrong when
you sit down.
Here here here are very. Ironic because.
I thought. This would be the last witness
you got to let me put you on the stand
to do quite frankly was Damian if
you will testify you haven't got
a chance. Raise your right hand you sound
very challenged you know it was not
about to stop
a guy I do these to your name various David
cousins under what name did you know
the defendant Madeline dicks if you ever
turned over to name. Did she ever lie to
you about her identity Yes How long as you
continue to lie to you in the morning
the police came Did she ever tell you
about her relations with Kaufman Oh she
didn't you propose marriage to the defendant
that you accepted Yes Still she didn't
tell you about court. When did you first
know the true relationship between. Same
morning the morning the police came Oh I
see them from the moment you met until the
day you were taken into custody
you didn't know the truth about
a kind of I object Your Honor don't write
every you cover your point or your honor
I'm merely trying to clarify for but Yuri
the true nature of the defendants will
see that one more question Dr
if you had known the truth
would have affected your love for the
defendant your honor I must protest I didn't
objection withdrawn and I doubt
because. If you had known the truth
would have affected your
love for the defendant
I was in love with Miss Damien
then and I'm in love with him now.
You know but this Mathilde no way.
Could you bring me. Yes
I really meant. I can't
believe you now would you
let me put you on the stand
you admit you want to cause a problem
that. You made love to go yet you have
a conversation about that because. You
know President you. Were telling us
Damian where you would love to Carmen know
where enough because. You know but you
won't because the problem nevertheless yet
tell you that you were not one man yet
you chose to visit the apartment of
a man you didn't love as you go of your
own free will. Because of the force you
would threaten you then why did
you get. I don't now I made
a mistake. You made
a mistake as you told us the several
occasions that you were Mr Crocker would
roughed up by
a mysterious intruder can you tell this
jury and I think definite about that person
anything at all you know I didn't see you
didn't see him out in the head is fine
you seem very certain about the man and the
drugs and what did he say I don't know
they were talking the hard way I
couldn't tell you the same as you heard
a voice you're willing to swear it was
a man and you couldn't hear
what he said but what sort of
a person you think would be calling at
that time of night a bill collector
a man selling magazines or perhaps even
a burglar find out then the contents of
a well meaning he must have been
a very timid big name because nothing was
stolen of course you realize that Mr
Carson kept his Jews in
a box of the store not all of them you
can't send that come when you think it's
a prop say that on
anything on you didn't buy
a new term so you didn't say to this baby
yes thank you card please this is the
first we've heard about a seat I asked for
a recess to examine the About Your Honor
we've been all over the bar but if there
is
a safe and if it has been run yet unknown
callers in here until tomorrow morning I
suggest interesting K.
Turning undefended exam they finally get.
What are they right about that you
want from the White House. I have
a statement but I want to come out the
right. Mind if I tag along on the wire
showed the plan but if you turned out to
be there now that's of course right we are
all right I don't know of any statement
here I didn't think you did if you want
unbiased opinion on the biggest. There's
a lot of gossip perhaps you know where
the statements are Biosystems taking the
location to this day
and you'll be along in
a minute or you're on death row we're waiting
maybe Mr Garrett could tell us where
the safe is I asked him he doesn't know I
don't understand that Mr Garrett you are
very close to coke and went to
that's right I'm sure there's
a safe in here I would have known about it
at least I would have seen the key to it
they are so very simple there is no say but
if you find out I guess I don't buy Mr
Mitchell something in this book case
the wrong ones Mr O'Brien but be.
Sure you know but then
you get caught on T.V.
Thank you. That looks to me very much like
a safe Mr Brime Yes it
does does. But not like
a safe has ever been robbed I don't think
a good burger would be towed behind
us for in fact we started from
a much you know I want our human to be you
when this fuck it up yes it. Will cost
you
a lift. I have some papers here and I put
in order you mind if I stay all right I
may wait for the flight thank you very
much and you going to be. All I was just
curious about something I've never seen
a safe like that before one that operated
with the key on the Think about it I
guess I have only the normal assumption
about a safe is that the lock works on
a combination Heres
a good smokes or two I was wondering how
you knew this would work for the key you
said you'd never seen the key to it they
say this. Summer said something and it me
old boy see there could be another
explanation really. That you were
lying when you said you've never seen
a safe before you're not
serious are you deaf I'm
a scientist has to go. When we get hold
of an odd fact we consider every possible
explanation makes some of our most important
discoveries outweigh what must be
fascinating work yes it is suppose I had
known about that see which I didn't what
would that prove frankly nothing but it
does suggest. You were very close to
God when you know about to say maybe the
safe was robbed perhaps he found out about
it he was crawling with
a man and all the night he was
killed maybe that man was you that's
a very interesting theory
this isn't but as I said I'm
a scientist and we hit on
a theory like that the next thing we
do is test it. It's all I'm doing.
I see the new. You won't mind having
a move talk with the police no no I should
I think are pretty but then of course
if you've never seen me say before you
won't mind I'm checking it for you it
certainly meant. The
numbers Springs seventy three one hundred.
No hard feelings. Don't you think this sort
of thing is rather out of your line Oh
I guess maybe you're
right my doctor arrived.
From seven three one
hundred wasn't much to go.
I guess maybe I
underestimated you directly.
OK actually rescued. From exaggerated.
Pressure by an act of terrorism. It was
a crime or many not to. Dispose
of the people who are going to
make dining in the middle of
a new boat for you probably
a stepping attack today to young
Dr when you get the murderer in
a battle royal. I've been looking for
missing you seen it she's gone she ask you
this right where did she go I couldn't get
a word out of her but I know she's at the
airport more than an hour ago. Late.
Last.
Week. I can still hear you call
now to look at what you. Did not
get to me but. I can't do.
That like now that's what. I'm going
to wait. I want to be able to do.
That I can't even think
of. Maybe up to. And say
I'm going to say that
piece of. Good time and.
Place.
My order. But I'll try to see it wasn't
a. Mistake I want to. Make sure.
I am what you've been through I'm
very sure. I still think you're
making a mistake.